[{"answer": "Because he made a big deal about how I understand everything immediately. That's what impressed him", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Barber.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "And if I don't call..", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well I, if it's your day off I really...", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Barber.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Well I don't want to take too much off", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Barber.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What do you mean you show up", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I show up. I pretend I have the job. The guy's on vacation. If I have the job, it's fine. If I don't have the job, by the time he comes back, I'm ensconced", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Barber.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What's the worst thing that could happen", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "How can I help you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Barber.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I wasn't aware that, uh, my friend, this is my friend. He's starting here today", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I got a haircut", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Barber.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh there's nothing to see", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh yeah? Can I see it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Barber.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Come on. Let me see it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Apologize", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Barber.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "He make me cry too. You want something to drink", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yeah, so", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Barber.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No. He doesn't know", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I think he knew", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Barber.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Who do you know? He knows my hair", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Number one", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Barber.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "All right. Flush twice. He goes in the bathroom", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh my god, he knows.  Go.  One second", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Barber.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No I wasn't there", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Don't my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Barber.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yes it's true", "qsentId": 26}]